DIPTI AGARWAL (MBA, B.Com)



diptiagarwal004@gmail.com



8655857815



linkedin.com/in/dipti-agarwal-a7761a73

Summary

I'm a marketing professional with 12 years of experience and an MBA in Marketing. I have skills in research, Microsoft Excel, Word, pivots, operations, customer relationship management, negotiation, communication, analysis and coordination. I also implement new software or processes and find creative solutions. I deliver results and grow my network of clients and partners. I' m marketing professional with a proven track record and friendly personality.

Experience

Business Coordinator

KYOTO Technologies

Jan 2022 - Present (1 year 5 months)

- · Managing a Team.
- Preparing Proposals/Quotations for UAE, Qatar client.
- Sales Performance Reports.
- Collaborate with the sales / Internal team.
- Vendor Portals and Tenders Management
- Vendor Coordination for Price and Negotiation
- CRM Management.
- · Onboarding New Vendors.
- Order Processing through PAF



Deputy Manager - Marketing Coordinator

Bharat Wire Ropes Ltd

Jul 2019 - Jan 2022 (2 years 7 months)

- Process and track customer orders, ensuring timely delivery.
- Handled complex marketing operations, streamlined process, and achieved production targets.
- Manage Internal portals and give strategic inputs in implementing new software.
- Inventory management, Order verification and production
- Coordination with internal/external teams, Resolving order-related issues.
- · Reporting and analysis for strategic decision-making
- Skilled in designing and developing monthly production plans to achieve production targets.
- Training and Development for Internal Staff.
- Implement strategies for lowering Cost and Maintain KPI's.

Executive sales Coordinator

Embee Software Pvt. Ltd.

Apr 2018 - May 2019 (1 year 1 months)

- · Identifying key customers
- Generate Leads and Create opportunity through social media (LinkedIn and so on)
- Customer relationship management
- · Prepare and manage proposals.
- Follow up with the customers for up selling and cross-selling.
- Manage Vendor and Tender Portals
- Coordinate with vendors and customers for price, negotiation and closure.
- Provide effective support to the sales team by acting as a team member.
- Customer order processing through SAP & OPF
- Maintain customer order in CRM.
- Email Marketing, Campaigns.
- Internal Coordination with Procurement team.

Sales Coordinator

Solutions Middle East

Sep 2016 - Apr 2018 (1 year 8 months)

- Managing India as well as UAE Team.
- Preparing Proposals/Quotations for India, UAE, Qatar client.
- Sales Pipeline and Team Performance Reports:
- Manage existing customers for repeat orders or renewal of licenses.
- Collaborate with the sales / Internal team.
- Vendor Portals and Tenders Management
- Vendor Coordination for Price and Negotiation
- CRM Management.
- Follow-ups for Orders and Payments with Customers.
- Order Processing

Operation Assistant

Bhavmark System Pvt Ltd

Oct 2011 - Sep 2016 (5 years)

- · Coordinating with Customers, Marketing Team and Distributors.
- · Preparing Quotations and Proforma Invoices
- Handling Email Correspondence related to customer or internal.
- Follow-ups for Outstanding Payments
- · Sales Report for Management with areas of Improvement.
- Worked on Various Tenders (Eg: BHEL)
- Sales Invoice Preparation
- Reconcile Bank entries with bank statement every month.
- Work on Bank documents for loan, CC Limit, Export/Import duty.
- Work with Auditors during Financials
- Coordinate with Supplier for Goods, Invoice and Discounts
- Cross Verifying Trial Balance in case of Mismatches

Education



St. Francis Institute Of Management and Research

Master of Business Administration - MBA, Marketing 2016 - 2019



DURGADEVI SARAF INSTITUTE OF MANAGEMENT STUDIES, MUMBAI

Bachelor of Commerce (B.Com.), Business/Commerce, General 2008 - 2011

Skills

Critical Thinking • SAP ERP • Microsoft Dynamics CRM • Marketing Management • Communication • Vendor Management • Problem Solving • Customer Relationship Management (CRM) • Leadership • Team Management

Honors & Awards

Achievements & Certifications:

- Awarded Saraswati Amma Gold medal for "1st Rank" in MBA (2016-2019)
- Certificate for presenting research paper on sustainable growth of start-up
- Awarded as "Best Student of the Year" in 2019.
- Certificate for being Topper in Part Time MBA for 1st and 2nd Year.
- Certification in MDP for Market place simulation Live
- For participants in college events and for extra-curricular activities.
- Best Performance in Other Departments in a year 2015 (Bhavmark Co.)
- Best Performance award in a year 2013 (Bhavmark Co)